prfriend.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy - PR Friend

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover all visitors to this website, all subscribers to lists or newsletters, all members or affiliates and all customers. It sets out how PRfriend uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.

### How to Contact Us:

We can be contacted at <http://www.prfriend.com/contact/>

### Overview

PRfriend knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.

We are committed to protecting your privacy.

We do not store financial details of customers on the PRfriend site as all orders are carried out on Ultracart’s Secure Server.

We will not e-mail you unless you have given us your consent or in reply to a specific request from you.  
We use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site and cookies to record session information.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### More Detailed Information

#### Volunteered Information

We collect information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

#### Product Order Information

All product orders are carried out on Ultracart’s Secure Server and subject to their Privacy Policy – <http://www.ultracart.com/privacy.html>

#### E-mail Communications:

You will only receive Email from us if you communicate with us or give us permission to do so. If you sign up for our newsletter, you can cancel at any time and a cancellation link is provided on each message sent out.

#### Does PRfriend Share the Information It Receives?

We do not share information with any other bodies.

#### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### Third-party advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
  * Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/blocked-cookies.html).

#### Future Privacy Policy Changes

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use these new purposes only for data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

#### Queries

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can [contact](http://www.prfriend.com/contact/) PRfriend for clarification.
